indiarealtysearch.com 2012-10-07

# 

  | 

**Privacy Policy India Reality Search**

This privacy policy of our Organization tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any change will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

**Collection of Information :**

In order to provide personalized browsing experience we collect personally identifiable information, like Name,Contact No., Postal Addresses, Email Addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. To extend this personalized experience we may track the IP address of a user's computer and save certain information on your system in the form of cookies. A user has the option of accepting or declining the cookies of this website by changing the settings of your browser. Additionally some of our web pages will require you to complete a registration form. The information you provide is used to fulfil you specific request. This information is only used to fulfil your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. 

**Tracking Of Cookie :**

We shall use IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Customer’s IP address may be also used to gather broad demographic information. Our Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Our tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system,Geographical Location, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 

**Sharing Of Information :**

By using Our website and inputting personal information the user understands that IndiaRealtySearch.com will use such information for internal purposes and with your permission or upon your request may also provide that information to affiliated companies or persons. IndiaRealtySearch.com takes full care to see that user information is not transmitted to unauthorized persons or the general public but is not liable for such information transmission due to theft, hacking or software errors. We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: 

(1) Permitted or required by law; or, 

(2) Trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, 

(3) Investigating fraud which has already taken place. 

The information is not provided to Other Companies for marketing purposes. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security :**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

If we change our privacy policy, we will instantly post a link to those changes on our Website so that you are always aware of what information we are collecting, how we use that kind of information, and under what circumstances, if any arises, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of your registration when it was collected, we will notify you by way of an email. We will give you a choice as to whether or not we can use information in this different manner and act accordingly.
